# YAZAN WIDYAN

**REACT NATIVE AND REACT JS DEVELOPER** 



### CONTACT



#### **Phone**

+962795382171



#### **Email**

yazanwidyan07@gmail.com



#### **Address**



## Linkdin



## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- React Native
- React JS
- Redux
- HTML
- CSS
- ECMAscript & Typescript
- Bootstrap & SASS
- Responsive Designs



### LANGUAGE

- English







# **SUMMARY**

To be involved in work where I can utilize skills and be creatively involved with a system that effectively contributes to the growth of the company and implements the experience gained in the computer engineering field to develop projects with efficiency and quality.



### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Aug 2020 - Present React Native & React JS Developer **IHR (INTERNATIONAL HUMAN RESOURCES)**

- Create and develop high-end mobile applications
- . Highly scalable and cost-efficient apps that best suit business needs
- . Translating customer needs into interactive web apps

# (5) React Native & React JS Developer Dec 2019 - Aug 2020 WTM / CG IMAGINE + INVENT

- · Writing website code with programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript and
- Producing, maintaining and modifying websites and user interfaces.
- Responsible for developing new user-facing feature.
- Determining the structure and design of web pages, building reusable codes



### **EDUCATION**

Dec 2019 - Mar 2020 (2)**INTERNSHIP** 

WTM / CG imagine + invent

2017 (2) **BACHELOR'S OF ENGLISH/ARABIC TRANSLATION** 

YARMOUK UNIVERSITY